Guide to the Records of Governor James S. Gilmore, 1998-2002
Library of Virginia
- Series IIIa. Press Office: News clipping subject and chronological files (Accession 40170), 1998-2001., Extent: 15 cu. ft. (Box 86-100)
  - Secretary of Commerce and Trade
    - Subject files: Omega Fire Sprinklers, 1998-1999. (Box 86, Folder 54)
    - Subject files: OSHA, 2000. (Box 86, Folder 55)
    - Subject files: Professional and Occupational Regulation, Dept. of, 19. (Box 86, Folder 56)
    - Subject files: Racing Commission (Colonial Downs), 1998-2001. (Box 86, Folder 57)
    - Subject files: Resources Authoriy, 1999. (Box 86, Folder 58)
    - Subject files: Silver Project, 1998-2000. (Box 86, Folder 59)
    - Subject files: Southeastern U.S.-Korea, 1998. (Box 86, Folder 60)
    - Subject files: Space Port - Wallops Island, 1998-1999. (Box 86, Folder 61)
    - Subject files: State Corporation Commission, 1998-1999. (Box 86, Folder 62)
    - Subject files: Technology, 1998-2000. (Box 86, Folder 63)
    - Subject files: Telecommunications, 1998-1999. (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Subject files: Textile Workers Relief Act, 2000. (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Subject files: Tourism and travel, 1998-2001. (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Subject files: Trade Mission to East Asia, 2000. (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Subject files: Trade Mission to South America, 1999. (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Subject files: Tultex, 199-2000. (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Subject files: Utilities, 1998-2001. (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Subject files: Virginia Economic Development Partnership, 1998-2000. (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Subject files: Virginia Strategy Board, 1998. (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Subject files: Volvo, 1999-2000. (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Subject files: Water projects - Southside Virginia, 19. (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Subject files: Wineries, 2000. (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Chronological files, 1998 Jan-Mar. (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Chronological files, 1998 Apr-June. (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Chronological files, 1998 July-Sept. (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Chronological files, 1998 Oct-Dec. (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Chronological files, 1999 Jan-Mar. (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Chronological files, 1999 Apr-June. (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - Chronological files, 1999 July-Sept. (Box 87, Folder 19)
    - Chronological files, 1999 Oct-Dec. (Box 87, Folder 20)
    - Chronological files, 2000 Jan-Mar. (Box 87, Folder 21)
    - Chronological files, 2000 Apr-June. (Box 87, Folder 22)
    - Chronological files, 2000 July-Sept. (Box 87, Folder 23)
    - Chronological files, 2000 Oct-Dec. (Box 87, Folder 24)
    - Chronological files, 2001 Jan-Mar. (Box 87, Folder 25)
    - Chronological files, 2001 Apr-June. (Box 87, Folder 26)
    - Chronological files, 2001 July-Sept. (Box 87, Folder 27)
    - Chronological files, 2001 Oct-Dec. (Box 87, Folder 28)
  - Secretary of Education
    - Subject files: American Legislative Exchange, 2000 Mar. (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Subject files: Capitol College (Capitol Institute of Technology), 2000. (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Subject files: Charter schools, 1998-1999. (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Subject files: Charter schools, 2000-2001. (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Subject files: Children First Conference, 1998. (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Subject files: Christopher Newport University, 1998-2001. (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Subject files: Colleges - General, 2000-2001. (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Subject files: Community Colleges - General, 1998-2001. (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Subject files: Community Colleges - Northern Virginia Community College, 1999. (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Subject files: Community Colleges - Patrick Henry Community College, 2000. (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Subject files: Community Colleges - Tidewater Community College, 1998-2000. (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Subject files: Correspondence, 1999-2000. (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Subject files: Coverdale-Torricelli Education Savings Account, 1998. (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Subject files: Eastern Virginia Medical School, 2000. (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Subject files: Editorials, 1998. (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - Subject files: Editorials, 1999. (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Subject files: Editorials, 2000. (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - Subject files: Editorials, 2001. (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - Subject files: Education, State Board of, 1998-2001. (Box 88, Folder 19)
    - Subject files: George Mason University, 1998-2000. (Box 88, Folder 20)
    - Subject files: George Washington University, 2001. (Box 88, Folder 21)
    - Subject files: Governor's Fellows Program, 98. (Box 88, Folder 22)
    - Subject files: Governor's School, 1998-2001. (Box 88, Folder 23)
    - Subject files: Hampton University, 1999-2001. (Box 88, Folder 24)
    - Subject files: Higher Education - Affirmative Action, 1999. (Box 88, Folder 25)
    - Subject files: Higher Education - Blue Ribbon Commission, 1998-2001. (Box 88, Folder 26)
    - Subject files: Higher Education - Budget amemdments, 1998. (Box 88, Folder 27)
    - Subject files: Higher Education, State Council on, 1998. (Box 88, Folder 28)
    - Subject files: Higher Education, State Council on, 1999. (Box 88, Folder 29)
    - Subject files: Higher Education, State Council on, 2000. (Box 88, Folder 30)
    - Subject files: Home Schooling, 1998-2000. (Box 88, Folder 31)
    - Subject files: James Madison University, 1998-2001. (Box 88, Folder 32)
    - Subject files: Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1998-2001. (Box 88, Folder 33)
    - Subject files: Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation - Celebration 2007, 2000-2001. (Box 88, Folder 34)
    - Subject files: Library of Virginia, 1998-1999. (Box 88, Folder 35)
    - Subject files: Longwood College, 1998-2001. (Box 88, Folder 36)
    - Subject files: Mary Washington College, 1998-2001. (Box 88, Folder 37)
    - Subject files: Minute of Silence - Prayer bill, 2000-2001. (Box 88, Folder 38)
    - Subject files: Norfolk State University, 1998-2001. (Box 88, Folder 39)
    - Subject files: Old Dominion University, 1998-2001. (Box 88, Folder 40)
    - Subject files: Pledge of Allegiance bill, 2001. (Box 88, Folder 41)
    - Subject files: Pre-paid tuition - Virginia Higher Education Trust Fund, 1998-2001. (Box 88, Folder 42)
    - Subject files: Public Instruction, Superintendent of, 1999-2000. (Box 88, Folder 43)
    - Subject files: Radford University, 1998-2001. (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Subject files: Regent University, 1998-2001. (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Subject files: SATs, 2000=2001. (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Subject files: School Construction Commission, 1998. (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Subject files: School Vouchers, 1998-2000. (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Subject files: Schools - Busing, 2000. (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Subject files: Schools - Construction, 1998-2000. (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Subject files: Schools - Funding, 1999-2001. (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Subject files: Schools - General, 2000-2001. (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Subject files: Science Museum, 1999-2000. (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Subject files: Science Museum - Discovery Park proposal, 1998. (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Subject files: Special Education, 2000. (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Subject files: Standards of Learning (SOLs), 2001. (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Subject files: Standards of Learning (SOLs) - FOIA requests, 2000. (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - Subject files: Teachers - Issues, 1998-2001. (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Subject files: Teachers - Salaries, 2000-2001. (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Subject files: Technology in Education, 2000. (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Subject files: Tuition costs/college funding, 1998-2000. (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Subject files: Tuition credits - Private School Tax Credits, 2000-2001. (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - Subject files: University of Richmond, 1998-2001. (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - Subject files: University of Virginia - General, 1998-2001. (Box 89, Folder 21)
    - Subject files: University of Virginia - Admissions, 1999-2000. (Box 89, Folder 22)
    - Subject files: University of Virginia - Athletics, 1999. (Box 89, Folder 23)
    - Subject files: University of Virginia - Baby switch case, 1998-2001. (Box 89, Folder 24)
    - Subject files: University of Virginia - Boards, 1998-2001. (Box 89, Folder 25)
    - Subject files: University of Virginia - Cavalier Daily, 2001. (Box 89, Folder 26)
    - Subject files: University of Virginia - Costs and contributions, 1998-2000. (Box 89, Folder 27)
    - Subject files: University of Virginia - Facts and figures, 1998-2001. (Box 89, Folder 28)
    - Subject files: University of Virginia - Governor's address, 1998. (Box 89, Folder 29)
    - Subject files: University of Virginia - Hospital, 1998-2001. (Box 89, Folder 30)
    - Subject files: University of Virginia - Minority issues, 1999-2000. (Box 89, Folder 31)
    - Subject files: University of Virginia - Public safety (alcohol, violence and drugs), 1998-1999. (Box 89, Folder 32)
    - Subject files: University of Virginia - Research Park, 1998-2001. (Box 89, Folder 33)
    - Subject files: University of Virginia - Qatar, 1998-1999. (Box 89, Folder 34)
    - Subject files: University of Virginia - Technology, 1999. (Box 89, Folder 35)
    - Subject files: University of Virginia - Wise Campus, 1999-2001. (Box 89, Folder 36)
    - Subject files: Virginia Commonwealth University, 1998-2001. (Box 89, Folder 37)
    - Subject files: Virginia Commonwealth University - Medicial College of Virginia, 1998-2001. (Box 89, Folder 38)
    - Subject files: Virginia Education Association, 2000-2001. (Box 89, Folder 39)
    - Subject files: Virginia Institute of Forensic Science, 1999. (Box 89, Folder 40)
    - Subject files: Virginia Military Institute, 1998-2001. (Box 89, Folder 41)
    - Subject files: Virgnia Museum of Fine Arts, 1999-2001. (Box 89, Folder 42)
    - Subject files: Virginia Museum of Fine Arts - Sally Mann photographs, 2000. (Box 89, Folder 43)
    - Subject files: Virginia State University, 2001. (Box 89, Folder 44)
    - Subject files: Virginia Tech, 1998-2001. (Box 89, Folder 45)
    - Subject files: Virginia Tech - Carilion Biomedical Institute, 1999-2000. (Box 89, Folder 46)
    - Subject files: Virginia Union University, 1998-2001. (Box 89, Folder 47)
    - Subject files: William and Mary College, 1998-2001. (Box 89, Folder 48)
    - Chronological files, 2000 Jan-Mar. (Box 89, Folder 49)
    - Chronological files, 2000 Apr-June. (Box 89, Folder 50)
    - Chronological files, 2000 July-Sept. (Box 89, Folder 51)
    - Chronological files, 2000 Oct-Dec. (Box 89, Folder 52)
    - Chronological files, 2001 Jan-Mar. (Box 89, Folder 53)
    - Chronological files, 2001 Apr-June. (Box 89, Folder 54)
    - Chronological files, 2001 July-Sept. (Box 89, Folder 55)
    - Chronological files, 2001 Oct-Dec. (Box 89, Folder 56)
  - Secretary of Finance
    - Subject files: American Legislative Exchange Council, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Subject files: Arts funding, 1998-2000 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Subject files: Audit of the Governor's Office, 2000 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Subject files: Budget and planning, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Subject files: Budget Report, 2001 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Subject files: Business Council, Virginia, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Subject files: Car Tax, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Subject files: Car Tax, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Subject files: Car Tax, 2000 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Subject files: Car Tax, 2001 Jan (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Subject files: Car Tax, 2001 Feb (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Subject files: Car Tax, 2001 Mar-Dec (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Subject files: Car Tax - Law suit, 2001 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Subject files: Commemorative Coin Program, 1998-2000 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Subject files: Economics, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Subject files: Editorials, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Subject files: Editorials, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Subject files: Editorials, 2000 (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Subject files: Editorials, 2001 (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Subject files: Editorials - Car Tax, 1998-2001 (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Subject files: Finance Reform Commission, 2001 (Box 90, Folder 21)
    - Subject files: Food Tax, 1998-2000 (Box 90, Folder 22)
    - Subject files: Governor's Budget, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 23)
    - Subject files: Governor's Budget, 2000 (Box 90, Folder 24)
    - Subject files: Governor's Budget, 2000 Dec (Box 90, Folder 25)
    - Subject files: (1 of 4), 2001 (Box 90, Folder 26)
    - Subject files: Governor's Budget (2 of 4), 2001 (Box 90, Folder 27)
    - Subject files: Governor's Budget (3 of 4), 2001 (Box 90, Folder 28)
    - Subject files: Governor's Budget (4 of 4), 2001 (Box 90, Folder 29)
    - Subject files: Non-state agency funding, 2001 (Box 90, Folder 30)
    - Subject files: Regional taxes, 2000 (Box 90, Folder 31)
    - Subject files: Revenue report, 2001 (Box 90, Folder 32)
    - Subject files: Strategic plan, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 33)
    - Subject files: Tax Reform Commission, 2001 (Box 90, Folder 34)
    - Subject files: Taxation, 1998-2001 (Box 90, Folder 35)
    - Subject files: Thomas Jefferson Institute for Public Policy, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 36)
    - Subject files: Treasury, 1999-2001 (Box 90, Folder 37)
    - Chronological files, 1998 Jan-Aug (Box 90, Folder 38)
    - Chronological files, 1998 Sept-Dec (Box 90, Folder 39)
    - Chronological files - Car Tax, 1998 Jan-Mar (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Chronological files - Car Tax, 1998 Apr-June (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Chronological files - Car Tax, 1998 July-Sept (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Chronological files - Car Tax, 1998 Oct-Dec (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Chronological files, 1999 Jan-Mar (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Chronological files, 1999 Apr-Sept (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Chronological files, 1999 Oct-Dec (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Chronological files, 2000 Jan-Mar (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Chronological files, 2000 Apr-June (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Chronological files, 2000 July-Sept (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Chronological files, 2000 Oct-Dec (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Chronological files, 2001 Jan-June (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Chronological files, 2001 July-Sept (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Chronological files, 2001 Oct-Dec (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources
    - Subject files: Abortion, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Subject files: Abortion, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Subject files: Abortion, 2000 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Subject files: Abortion, 2001 (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Subject files: Abstinence/birth control, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - Subject files: Adoptions, 1998-1999 (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - Subject files: Anthrax, 2001 (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - Subject files: Bayview, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 22)
    - Subject files: Caregiver grants, 2000 (Box 91, Folder 23)
    - Subject files: Central State Hospital, 1998-2001 (Box 91, Folder 24)
    - Subject files: Charter Westbrook, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 25)
    - Subject files: Chaudhary, Nazir MD, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 26)
    - Subject files: Child Protective Services/Child abuse, 1998-2001 (Box 91, Folder 27)
    - Subject files: Children's Health Care Plan, 1998-2001 (Box 91, Folder 28)
    - Subject files: Daycare, 1998-2000 (Box 91, Folder 29)
    - Subject files: Eastern State Hospital, 1998-2001 (Box 91, Folder 30)
    - Subject files: Editorials, 2001 (Box 91, Folder 31)
    - Subject files: Editorials, 2000 (Box 91, Folder 32)
    - Subject files: Editorials, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 33)
    - Subject files: Editorials, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 34)
    - Subject files: Employment and training, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 35)
    - Subject files: Executive Order 58 - Family Impact, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 36)
    - Subject files: Finn, Hugh (1 of 2), 1998-2000 (Box 91, Folder 37)
    - Subject files: Finn, Hugh (2 of 2), 1998-2000 (Box 91, Folder 38)
    - Subject files: Geller Report, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 39)
    - Subject files: Group homes, 2000 (Box 91, Folder 40)
    - Subject files: Hammond Commission, 1998-1999 (Box 91, Folder 41)
    - Subject files: Health Care - Elderly, 1998-2001 (Box 91, Folder 42)
    - Subject files: Health Care - General, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 43)
    - Subject files: Health Care - General, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 44)
    - Subject files: Health Care - General, 2000 (Box 91, Folder 45)
    - Subject files: Health Care - General, 2001 (Box 91, Folder 46)
    - Subject files: Health Commissioner, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 47)
    - Subject files: Health, Dept. of, 2000 (Box 91, Folder 48)
    - Subject files: Health Professions, Dept. of, 1998-1999 (Box 91, Folder 49)
    - Subject files: HMOs, 1999-2001 (Box 91, Folder 50)
    - Subject files: Hospitals, 2000-2001 (Box 91, Folder 51)
    - Subject files: Kessler, Keith, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Subject files: Medicaid and Medicare, 1998-2001 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Subject files: Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of, 1998-2000 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Subject files: Medical services and facilities, 1998-2000 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Subject files: Mental Health, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Subject files: Mental Health, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Subject files: Mental Health, 2000 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Subject files: Mental Health, 2001 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Subject files: Mental Health - Comprehensive Plan, 2000 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Subject files: Mental Health - Comprehensive Plan, 2001 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Subject files: Mental Health - Hospitals, 1998-2001 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Subject files: Nursing, 2001 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Subject files: Nursing homes, 1998-2001 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Subject files: Oxycontin, 2001 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Subject files: Pharmacy Connect, 2001 (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Subject files: Sex education, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Subject files: Social Services, Dept. of, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Subject files: Social Services, Dept. of, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - Subject files: Social Services, Dept. of, 2000 (Box 92, Folder 19)
    - Subject files: Social Services, Dept. of, 2001 (Box 92, Folder 20)
    - Subject files: Stem cell research, 2001 (Box 92, Folder 21)
    - Subject files: Substance abuse, 1998-2001 (Box 92, Folder 22)
    - Subject files: Vaccinations, 1998-2001 (Box 92, Folder 23)
    - Subject files: Virginia Hospital and Healthcare Association, 2000 (Box 92, Folder 24)
    - Subject files: Virginians with disabilities, 1998-2001 (Box 92, Folder 25)
    - Subject files: Welfare Reform, 1999-2000 (Box 92, Folder 26)
    - Subject files: Western State Hospital, 1998-2001 (Box 92, Folder 27)
    - Chronological files, 1998 Jan-Mar (Box 92, Folder 28)
    - Chronological files, 1998 Apr-June (Box 92, Folder 29)
    - Chronological files, 1998 July-Sept (Box 92, Folder 30)
    - Chronological files, 1998 Oct-Dec (Box 92, Folder 31)
    - Chronological files, 1999 Jan-Mar (Box 92, Folder 32)
    - Chronological files, 1900 Apr-June (Box 92, Folder 33)
    - Chronological files, 1999 July-Sept (Box 92, Folder 34)
    - Chronological files, 1999 Oct-Dec (Box 92, Folder 35)
    - Chronological files, 2000 Jan-Mar (Box 92, Folder 36)
    - Chronological files, 2000 Apr-Sept (Box 92, Folder 37)
    - Chronological files, 2000 Oct-Dec (Box 92, Folder 38)
    - Chronological files, 2001 Jan-June (Box 92, Folder 39)
    - Chronological files, 2001 July-Sept (Box 92, Folder 40)
    - Chronological files, 2001 Oct-Dec (Box 92, Folder 41)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources
    - Subject files: Apples, 1998-1999 (Box 92, Folder 42)
    - Subject files: Chesapeake Bay, 1998-2001 (Box 92, Folder 43)
    - Subject files: Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of, 1998-2000 (Box 92, Folder 44)
    - Subject files: Crabs, 1998-2001 (Box 92, Folder 45)
    - Subject files: Defense Supply Center - Rayon Park, 2001 (Box 92, Folder 46)
    - Subject files: Editorials, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 47)
    - Subject files: Editorials, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 48)
    - Subject files: Editorials, 2000 (Box 92, Folder 49)
    - Subject files: Editorials, 2001 (Box 92, Folder 50)
    - Subject files: Environmental education, 1998-2001 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Subject files: Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1998-2000 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Subject files: Environemental Quality, Dept. of, 1998 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Subject files: Environmental Quality, Dept. of, 1999 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Subject files: Environmental Quality, Dept. of, 2000-2001 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Subject files: Fish, 1999-2001 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Subject files: Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of, 1998-2001 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Subject files: Garbage/Trash, 1998 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Subject files: Garbage/Trash, 1999 Jan-Mar (Box 93, Folder 8a)
    - Subject files: Garbage/Trash, 1999 Apr-Dec (Box 93, Folder 8b)
    - Subject files: Garbage/Trash, 2000 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Subject files: Garbage/Trash, 2001 (Box 93, Folder 9a)
    - Subject files: Greensways Project, 1999 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Subject files: Historic Resources, Dept. of, 1998 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Subject files: Hunting and Fishing bill, 2000 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Subject files: Land preservation, 2000 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Subject files: Marine Resources Commission, 1998-2000 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Subject files: National Parks in Virginia, 2000 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Subject files: Natural History, Virginia Museum of, 1998-2000 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Subject files: Newport News Reservoir, 1999-2001 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Subject files: Oysters, 1998-2000 (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - Subject files: Ozone Transport Commission, 1998 (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - Subject files: Pfiesteria, 1998-2000 (Box 93, Folder 20)
    - Subject files: Potomac River Fisheries Commission, 1998 (Box 93, Folder 21)
    - Subject files: Poultry, 1998-2001 (Box 93, Folder 22)
    - Subject files: Rivers, 1998-2001 (Box 93, Folder 23)
    - Subject files: Shark attacks, 2001 (Box 93, Folder 24)
    - Subject files: Sludge, 2001 (Box 93, Folder 25)
    - Subject files: "Trash" lawsuit, 1999-2000 (Box 93, Folder 26)
    - Subject files: Water issues, 2001 (Box 93, Folder 27)
    - Subject files: Wetlands, 1999-2001 (Box 93, Folder 28)
    - Chronological files, 1998 Jan-Mar (Box 93, Folder 29)
    - Chronological files, 1998 Apr-June (Box 93, Folder 30)
    - Chronological files, 1998 July-Sept (Box 93, Folder 31)
    - Chronological files, 1998 Oct-Dec (Box 93, Folder 32)
    - Chronological files, 1999 Jan-Mar (Box 93, Folder 33)
    - Chronological files, 1999 Apr-June (Box 93, Folder 34)
    - Chronological files, 1999 July-Sept (Box 93, Folder 35)
    - Chronological files, 1999 Oct-Dec (Box 93, Folder 36)
    - Chronological files, 2000 (Box 93, Folder 37)
    - Chronological files, 2001 (Box 93, Folder 38)
  - Secretary of Public Safety
    - Subject files: Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of,1998-2001 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Subject files: Alcohol issues - High schools and colleges, 1998-2000 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Subject files: Armstrong High School shooting, 1998 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Subject files: Bon Air Juvenile Center - FOIA, 1999 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Subject files: Capitol Police, 1999-2001 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Subject files: Correctional Education, Dept. of, 1999-2001 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Subject files: Correctional Enterprises, Dept. of, 1998 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Subject files: Corrections, Dept. of, 1998-2001 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Subject files: Criminal Justice Services, Dept. of, 1998-2001 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Subject files: Criminal Justice System in Virginia, 2000 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Subject files: Cullipher, Ricky,1999 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Subject files: Dandridge, Wallace, 1999 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Subject files: Death penalty, 1998-2001 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Subject files: Death penalty in Virginia - Report, 2000 (Box 94, Folder 14)